Guide to the Sports Information Office: Photographic Negatives collection, circa 1924-1992, 1995, undated UA.13.02.0018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Football Negatives, circa 1924-1992; 1995; undated; 8
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 28
    - Finn, Tom, 1935, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05200)
    - Fischer, Charlie, 1937, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05201)
    - Fitch, Bob, 1969 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01920)
    - Fitch, Bob, 1970 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01921)
    - Fitch, Bob, 1971 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01922)
    - Fitzpatrick, Mike, 1967 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01923)
    - Fitzpatrick, Mike, 1969 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01924)
    - Fletcher, Frank (Hank), 1970 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01925)
    - Fletcher, Frank (Hank), 1971 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01926)
    - Fletcher, Frank (Hank), 1972 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01927)
    - Fogle, Bob, circa 1963-1964 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01928)
    - Folger, Fred Jr. (receiving Noble Award), 1948, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05202)
    - Folger, Fred Jr., 1948 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01929)
    - Fondren, Frank, 1966, undated (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01930)
    - Forbis, Jim, 1969 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01931)
    - Forbis, Jim, 1970 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01932)
    - Forbis, Jim, 1971 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01933)
    - Fordham, Ben, 1972 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01934)
    - Fordham, Ben, 1972 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01935)
    - Fordham, Ben, 1973 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01936)
    - Fordham, Ben, 1974 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01937)
    - Forte, Maurice "Mo" (Assistant Coach), 1976 Aug. (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01938)
    - Forte, Maurice "Mo" (Assistant Coach), 1977 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01939)
    - Fox, Daryl, 1968, 1969 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01940)
    - Foyle, Bob, 1966, 1967 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01941)
    - Foyle, Bob, 1973 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01942)
    - Foyle, Bob (with Chuck Stavins), 1966 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01943)
    - Francis, Jerry, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01944)
    - Franks, Carl, 1980 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01945)
    - Franks, Carl, 1981 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01946)
    - Frederick, Ron, 1979 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01947)
    - Frederick, Ron, 1980 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01948)
    - Frederick, Ron, 1981 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01949)
    - Freeman, Willard, 1976 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01950)
    - Freeman, Willard, 1977 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01951)
    - Friedlund, Jack, 1949 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01952)
    - Friedman, Bert, circa 1930-1932, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05203)
    - Fritz, Rusty, 1979 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01953)
    - Frye, Bob, 1945, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05204)
    - Frye, Bob, 1945 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01954)
    - Frye, Bob, 1946, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05205)
    - Frye, Bob, 1948, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05206)
    - Fuller, Melville, 1946 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01955)
    - Funk, Muncy, 1945, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05207)
    - Furse, William, 1966 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01956)
    - Fusco, Vince, 1975 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01957)
    - Fusco, Vince, 1976 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01958)
    - Fusco, Vince (with unidentified girl "for pic after 5 field goals"), 1976 Oct. (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01959)
    - Futrell, Billy, circa 1961-1963 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01960)
    - Fuqua, Jim, 1961 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01961)
    - Fuqua, Mike, 1978 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01962)
    - Fuqua, Mike, 1980 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01963)
    - Fuqua, Mike, 1981 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01964)
    - Gantt, Bob, 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05208)
    - Gantt, Bob, 1942 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01965)
    - Gantt, Bob, 1943, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05209)
    - Gantt, Bob (with Gordon Carver), 1943, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05210)
    - Gantt, Bob, 1946, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05211)
    - Gantt, Bob (with Leo Long), 1946, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05212)
    - Garbinski, Jack, circa 1957-1958 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01966)
    - Garda, Bob, circa 1956-1960 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01967)
    - Gardiner, Dick, 1946 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01968)
    - Gardner, Bob, 1960 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01969)
    - Gardner, Jim, circa 1957-1959 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01970)
    - Gardner, Jim and Bob, circa 1959-1960 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01971)
    - Gardner, Sammy (Freshman team), 1934, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05213)
    - Gardner, Sammy, 1935, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05214)
    - Garey, Robert, 1945, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-05215)
    - Garner, Gilroy, circa 1960-1962 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01972)
    - Garner, Mike, 1968 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01973)
    - Garner, Mike, 1969 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01974)
    - Garrick, Don, 1937, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05217)
    - Garrison, Bob, 1957 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01975)
    - Garstkiewicz, Gary, 1978 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01976)
    - Garstkiewicz, Gary, 1979 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01977)
    - Garstkiewicz, Gary, 1980 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01978)
    - Garvin, Greg, 1971 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01979)
    - Garvin, Greg, 1972 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01980)
    - Garwood, Art, 1972 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01981)
    - Garwood, Art, 1973 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01982)
    - Garwood, Art, 1974 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01983)
    - Gawdun, George, 1977 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01984)
    - Gawdun, George, 1978 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01985)
    - Gawdun, George, 1979 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01986)
    - Gee, Chester, 1980 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01987)
    - Gee, J. B., 1960 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01988)
    - Gelbert, Dan, circa 1957-1959 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01989)
    - Germino, Romeo (Freshman team), 1934, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05218)
    - Gersbach, Carl, 1966 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01990)
    - Gibbs, David, 1969, 1970 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01991)
    - Gibbs, David, 1971 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01992)
    - Gibbs, George, 1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05219)
    - Gibson, Bob, 1950 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01993)
    - Gibson, Jim, 1950, 1951 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01994)
    - Giffin, Gordon (Manager), 1969 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01995)
    - Giffin, Jerry, 1969, 1970 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01996)
    - Giffin, Jerry, 1971 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01997)
    - Gill, Aubrey, circa 1940-1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05220)
    - Gill, Aubrey, circa 1940-1941 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01998)
    - Gillander, Robert, 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05221)
    - Gillespie, Jim [Assistant Coach?], 1973 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-01999)
    - Gilletee, John, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05222)
    - Gilson, Elmer, 1973 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-02000)
    - Gilson, Elmer, 1974 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-02001)
    - Gilson, Elmer, 1975 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-02002)
    - Glacken, Scotty, circa 1963-1965 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-02003)
    - Glacken, Scotty (color), 1965 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-02004)
    - Glacken, Scott (with Coach Bill Murray), 1965 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-02005)
    - Glankler, John, 1976 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-02006)
    - Glankler, John, 1977 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-02007)
    - Glankler, John, 1978 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-02008)
    - Gleason, Francis, 1952 (Box 15, Item UA13020018-N-02009)
    - Gleason, Jack, 1947, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05223)
    - Gleaves, Jerrell, circa 1956-1957 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02010)
    - Glossen, Ronnie, circa 1960-1962 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02011)
    - Goddard, Pete, 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05224)
    - Goddard, Pete (color), 1941 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02012)
    - Goddard, Pete (with Thomas Burns), 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05225)
    - Goins, Bob, 1970 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02013)
    - Goins, Bob, 1971 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02014)
    - Goins, Herb, 1965, 1966 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02015)
    - Goins, Herb, 1967 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02016)
    - Goldman, Joel, 1963 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02017)
    - Gombar, Greg, 1973 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02018)
    - Gombar, Greg, 1974 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02019)
    - Gombar, Greg, 1975 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02020)
    - Gonet, Ned, 1977 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02021)
    - Gonet, Ned, 1978 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02022)
    - Gonet, Ned, 1979 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02023)
    - Goode, Joe, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05226)
    - Gore, Art, 1974 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02024)
    - Gore, Art, 1975 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02025)
    - Gore, Art, 1976 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02026)
    - Gorman, Jack, 1939, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05227)
    - Grace, Chuck, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02027)
    - Grace, J. N., 1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05228)
    - Graham, Joe, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05229)
    - Graham, Joe, 1944 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02028)
    - Grant, Truett, 1952 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02029)
    - Grant, Wes, circa 1962-1963 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02030)
    - Grayson, Mike, 1981 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02031)
    - Green, Jeff, 1975 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02032)
    - Green, Jeff, 1976 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02033)
    - Green, Jeff, 1977 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02034)
    - Green, Ray, 1950 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02035)
    - Greenawalt, Dean, 1971 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02036)
    - Greene, George, 1950 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02037)
    - Greenwood, Joe, circa 1955-1956 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02038)
    - Greenwood, Porter, 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05230)
    - Gregory, Art, circa 1960-1962 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02039)
    - Greybeal, Joe, circa 1954-1955 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02040)
    - Griffith, Lloyd, 1958 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02041)
    - Griffith, Walter, 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05231)
    - Grimes, Dale, 1970 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02042)
    - Grimes, Dale, 1971 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02043)
    - Grimes, Dale, 1971 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02044)
    - Grimes, Dale, 1972 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02045)
    - Grimes, Dale, 1972 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02046)
    - Groome, Jim, 1946 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02047)
    - Gross, Johnny, circa 1938-1939, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05232)
    - Gross, Johnny (with Jack Lange), 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05233)
    - Grune, George, 1950 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02048)
    - Grupp, Bob, 1974 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02049)
    - Grupp, Bob, 1974 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02050)
    - Grupp, Bob, 1975 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02051)
    - Grupp, Bob, 1976 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02052)
    - Guglielmi, John, circa 1958-1959 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02053)
    - Gunter, Don, 1968 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02054)
    - Gunter, Don, 1969 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02055)
    - Guntekunst, John, circa 1963-1965 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02056)
    - Guntekunst, John (color), 1965 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02057)
    - Guntekunst, John (Assistant Coach), 1970, 1971, 1973 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02058)
    - Guntekunst, John (Assistant Coach), 1974, 1975, 1977 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02059)
    - Guthrie, Guy, 1968, 1969 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02060)
    - Guthrie, Guy, 1970 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02061)
    - Guthrie, Jim, circa 1960-1962 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02062)
    - Guy, Charles, 1966, 1967 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02063)
    - Guy, John (Assistant Coach), 1978 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02064)
    - Guy, Melwood, circa 1954-1956 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02065)
    - Gwinn, Chuck, 1954 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02066)
    - Haas, Bob, 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05234)
    - Haas, Bob (with Jasper "Jap" Davis), 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05235)
    - Hackney, Elmore "Honey" (Freshman team), 1937, 1935, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05236)
    - Hackney, Elmore" Honey," 1937, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05237)
    - Hadley, Hunter, 1953 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02067)
    - Hager, Dudley "Dud," 1950, 1953 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02068)
    - Haggerty, Cliff, 1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05238)
    - Haggerty, Cliff, 1943 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02069)
    - Haggerty, Cliff, 1945, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-02070)
    - Hagie, Bill, 1953 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02071)
    - Haglan, Dennis (Assistant Coach), 1976, 1977 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02072)
    - Haislip, Sam, 1950 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02073)
    - Haldeman, John, 1973 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02074)
    - Hall, [?], circa 1934-1935, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05239)
    - Hall, Jack, 1966, 1968, undated (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02075)
    - Hall, Jim, circa 1957-1958 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02076)
    - Hall, Tom, 1975 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02077)
    - Hall, Tom, 1975 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02078)
    - Hall, Tom, 1976 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02079)
    - Hall, Tom, 1977 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02080)
    - Halley, Frank, 1976 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02081)
    - Halley, Frank, 1977 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02082)
    - Hamilton, Eddie, 1940, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05240)
    - Hamilton, Scott, 1977 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02083)
    - Hamilton, Scott, 1978 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02084)
    - Hamrick, Waite, circa 1931-1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05241)
    - Hamschin, Mike, 1971 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02085)
    - Hamschin, Mike, 1972 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02086)
    - Hamschin, Mike, 1973 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02087)
    - Hands, Joe, 1953 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02088)
    - Hanenberg, Ted, 1972 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02089)
    - Hanenberg, Ted, 1973 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02090)
    - Hanenberg, Ted, 1974 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02091)
    - Hanenberg, William, 1970 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02092)
    - Hanenberg, William, 1971 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02093)
    - Hannon, Ron, 1977 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02094)
    - Hardin, Jim, 1954 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02095)
    - Hardin, Jim, 1976 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02096)
    - Hardison, Fred, 1944, 1946 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02097)
    - Hardison, Fred, 1946, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05242)
    - Hardy, Jack (alone and with Frank Killian), circa 1937-1940, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05243)
    - Harelson, Jeff, 1981 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02098)
    - Harley, Bob, 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05244)
    - Harp, Tom (Head Coach), 1966, 1969 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02099)
    - Harper, Tracy, 1978 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02100)
    - Harper, Tracy, 1979 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02101)
    - Harper, Tracy, 1980 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02102)
    - Harrington, David, 1973 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02103)
    - Harris, Bishop (Assistant Coach), 1973 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02104)
    - Harris, George, circa 1956-1957 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02105)
    - Harris, Jim, circa 1953-1954 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02106)
    - Harris, Norman, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05245)
    - Harris, Rich, circa 1962-1963 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02107)
    - Harris, Thomas "Skeet," 1970 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02108)
    - Harris, Thomas "Skeet," 1971 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02109)
    - Harris, Thomas "Skeet," 1972 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02110)
    - Harris, Tommy, 1949, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05246)
    - Harris, Tommy, 1949 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02111)
    - Harrison, Dick, 1948 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02112)
    - Harrison, Jack, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02113)
    - Harry, Reece, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05247)
    - Harry, Reece, 1946 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02114)
    - Hart, Leo, 1968, undated (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02115)
    - Hart, Leo, 1969 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02116)
    - Hart, Leo, 1970 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02117)
    - Hart, Leo (Assistant Coach), 1975, 1976, 1977 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02118)
    - Hartley, Howard (with family), 1943 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02119)
    - Hartley, Howard, 1946, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05248)
    - Hartley, Howard, 1946 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02120)
    - Hartley, Howard and Jimmy, 1946 Nov. 14, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05249)
    - Hartley, Jimmy, 1946, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05250)
    - Hartness, Carl, 1935, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05251)
    - Harton, Weldon, 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05252)
    - Harton, Weldon (with Bill Bryan), 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05253)
    - Hartwig, Charles, circa 1956-1957 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02121)
    - Hassell, Gerald, 1970 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02122)
    - Hasson, Newt, 1969 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02123)
    - Hasson, Newt, 1970 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02124)
    - Hasson, Newt, 1971 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02125)
    - Haupt, Dale (Assistant Coach), 1977 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02126)
    - Havens, Richard, 1960-1962 (Box 16, Item UA13020018-N-02127)
    - Hawkins, Ray, 1973 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02128)
    - Hawkins, Ray, 1974 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02129)
    - Hawkins, Ray, 1975 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02130)
    - Hawn, Bobby, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02131)
    - Hayden, Danny, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05254)
    - Hayden, Danny, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05255)
    - Hayden, Danny, 1946, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05256)
    - Hayes, Bob, circa 1929-1930, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05257)
    - Hayes, Bob, 1969 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02132)
    - Hayes, Bob, 1970 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02133)
    - Hayes, Don, 1972 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02134)
    - Hayes, Don, 1973 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02135)
    - Hayes, Mike, 1968 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02136)
    - Hayes, Mike, 1969 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02137)
    - Hayes, Robin, 1964 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02138)
    - Hayes, Roger, 1965-1967 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02139)
    - Hayes, Woody, 1960 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02140)
    - Haynes, Charles, 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05258)
    - Haynes, Charles, 1941 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02141)
    - Heady, Gary, 1971 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02142)
    - Heady, Gary, 1972 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02143)
    - Heady, Gary, 1973 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02144)
    - Hedgepeth, Herman, 1966 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02145)
    - Hedrick, Grady, 1939, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05259)
    - Heinsohn, Paul, 1979 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02146)
    - Heinsohn, Paul, 1980 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02147)
    - Heiss, Howard, 1949 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02148)
    - Helms, Tom, circa 1962-1963 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02149)
    - Hendrickson, Evan "Abe," 1937, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05260)
    - Hendrickson, Evan "Abe," 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05261)
    - Hendrickson, Horace "Horse," 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05262)
    - Hendrickson, Horace "Horse" (with unidentified man and Millis trophy), 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05263)
    - Hendrickson, Horace "Horse" (Assistant Coach, Freshman team, one with Wallace Wade), circa 1934-1936 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02150)
    - Heninger, Marty, 1981 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02151)
    - Heninger, Marty, 1981 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02152)
    - Hennemier, Jack, circa 1934-1935 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02153)
    - Hennemier, Jack, 1935, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05264)
    - Hennis, Cecil (Freshman team), 1937, 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05265)
    - Henry, Robert, 1966, 1967 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02154)
    - Henry, Tom, circa 1930-1931, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05266)
    - Hepler, Bob, 1967, 1968 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02155)
    - Hepler, Bob, 1969 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02156)
    - Hepler, Bob, 1969 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02157)
    - Herlong, Bettis (alone and with his young son), 1947, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05267)
    - Herlong, Bettis (alone and with his young son), 1947 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02158)
    - Hetrick, Jacque (Assistant Coach), 1966, 1968, 1970 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02159)
    - Hewitt, Tom, 1972 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02160)
    - Hicks, Bill, circa 1930-1932, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05268)
    - Hicks, Steve, 1977 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02161)
    - Hicks, Steve, 1978 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02162)
    - Hicklin, Ed, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02163)
    - Hightower, Tom, 1967 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02164)
    - Higginbothom, Bill, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05269)
    - Higgins, Louis, 1949 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02165)
    - Higgins, Norman, 1953 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02166)
    - Hill, Chris, 1968 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02167)
    - Hill, Chris, 1969 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02168)
    - Hill, Dan, 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05270)
    - Hill, Dan (with Eric Tipton, All-Americans), 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05271)
    - Hill, Dan (with Willa "Billy" Hedrick [female]), 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05272)
    - Hill, Dan (All America sweater), 1938-1939, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05273)
    - Hill, Dan, undated (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02169)
    - Hill, George (Assistant Coach), 1966 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02170)
    - Hill, John, 1972 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02171)
    - Hill, John, 1973 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02172)
    - Hill, John, 1973 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02173)
    - Hill, John, 1974 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02174)
    - Hipp, Charlie, 1940, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05274)
    - Hipps, Herbert, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05275)
    - Hipps, Herbert, 1945 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02175)
    - Hitchcock, Dan, 1967 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02176)
    - Hoch, Bill, 1954 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02177)
    - Hodges, Roland, circa 1944, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05276)
    - Hodges, Roland, 1946, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05277)
    - Hodges, Woody, 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05278)
    - Holben, Carl, 1950 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02178)
    - Hollingsworth, Harry (with William Adams), 1928, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05279)
    - Holley, Frank, 1975 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02179)
    - Holloman, Jim, 1952 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02180)
    - Holloway, Steve, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02181)
    - Holmes, Elwin (Freshman team), 1937, 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05280)
    - Holmes, Elwin (with Bob Alabaster), 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05281)
    - Holt, Keenan, 1979 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02182)
    - Holt, Keenan, 1981 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02183)
    - Holyroyd, [?] (Manager), 1946 Sept. 18, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05282)
    - Homa, Ken, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02184)
    - Honeycutt, Bobby, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02185)
    - Hood, Charlie, 1941, 1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05283)
    - Hoots, Ronnie, 1972 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02186)
    - Hoots, Ronnie, 1973 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02187)
    - Hoots, Ronnie, 1974 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02188)
    - Hoover, Al, 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05284)
    - Hord, Bobby, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02189)
    - Hord, Roy, 1956 (Box 17, Item UA13020018-N-02190)